[{"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "1:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "2:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "3:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "4:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "5:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "6:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "7:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "8:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "9:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "10:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "11:00", "targetTime": "12:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [12.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "1:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [1.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "2:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [2.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "3:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [3.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "4:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [4.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "5:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [5.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "6:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [6.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "7:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [7.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "8:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [8.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "9:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [9.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "10:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [10.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "拨动时钟", "stem": "拨动时针和分针，在钟表上表示", "startTime": "12:00", "targetTime": "11:30", "clockImg": "", "hourHandImg": "", "minuteHandImg": "", "type": "au-clock-select"}], "answers": [11.5, 6], "knowledges": ["整时、半时的应用"], "resource": "", "type": "操作", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-8-3-05"}]